General Reference; Collection ua950.002
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- E, 1852-2005; 5
  - Department of Environmental Health and Toxicology, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Environmental Studies Program, 2001 February 17 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Earth Day, Undated (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - ENY/ACRL Conference, Albany, 1989; 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - EOPSA ASP Articles, 1968-1985 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Epidemiology, Department of School of Public Health, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Equipment Management Office, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Erotic Cinema Circus, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Escort Patrol, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Estate Planner's Day, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Ethics Law, Undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Ethics Regulation, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Ethics - Faculty Statement of Ethics, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Ethnic Survey, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Evaluation Consortium at Albany, Undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Evacuation Procedures Residence Halls, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Examination Book, Undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Excellence Awards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Excellence Award Winners, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Excelsior School for Science and Mathematics for the State of New York, 1994 October 15 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Excelsior School for Science and Mathematics of New York State?, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Excuse Form, Undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Executive Briefing on Telecommunications, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Executive Vice - President, Office of the, 1972 January 13 - 1973 August 28 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Executive Vice - President, Office of the, 1973 September 14 - 1976 January 28 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Experiencing Albany: Past, Present, and Future, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Experimental College, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Experimental Department of State Normal School, 1852 November 30 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Extension Courses, 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Extension Teaching, 1934 - November 1961 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Extramural Activity, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Extramural Activates Policy Statement, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- F, 1864-2000; 6
  - Facilities Office, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Fact Sheets, 1930-1967 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Fact Sheets, 1967-1985 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Faculty, 1874; 1970 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Emeriti, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Faculty, New Members, 1939; 1960 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Faculty Advisers Handbook, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Faculty Association of the SUNY, 1958-1962 November 2 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Faculty Association of the SUNY, 1962-1968 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Faculty Bridge Group, 1968-1972 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Faculty By Laws, 1966; 1971; 1973 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Faculty By Laws, Undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Faculty Club, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Faculty Committee For Social and Charitable Concerns, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Faculty Club, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Faculty Dinner, 1938; 1946; 1952-1956; 1961; 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Faculty Festival, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Faculty Forum, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Faculty Handbook, Revision to, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Faculty Hour, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Faculty Lecture Committee, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Faculty Lecture, 1918; 1959 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Faculty - Newly Hired, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Faculty Organization For Academic Responsibility, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Faculty Publications, 1957-1964 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Faculty Publications, 1973 July 9-1975 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Faculty Research Board, Undated (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Faculty President Program, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Faculty Salaries, Undated (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Faculty Social Committee, 1951-1972 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Faculty - Staff Intramural Sports Program, 1964; 1967-1968; 1977 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Faculty Staff Ski Club, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Faculty Staff Ski Club, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Faculty Staff, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Faculty Staff, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Faculty Staff, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Faculty Students Committee, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Faculty Student Committee For Equal Opportunity, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Faculty - Student Committee on Tenure, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - "Fairy Bells", 1864 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Falconer - Fund, Raymond, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Feminism In The Eighties, Presidential Conference, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Feminist Alliance, 1975-1978; 1986 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Fencing Society, 1962-1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Final Report Field Expedition #7, 1967 May 1 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Film and Television Documentation Center, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Film and Television Documentation Center, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Films, Miscellaneous, 1971-1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Finance Department, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Finance & Business, Division of Five - Year Perspective, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Financial Aid Committee, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Financial Aid, ca. 1965-1988 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Financial Aid, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Financial Management, 1981-1984 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Fine Arts Program, 1964 March (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - "First Amendment and University Events" handed out in regards to Palestine Protests, 2024 April 29 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Five Safety in Residence Halls (Office of Environmental Health and Safety), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Firearms Policy, 1973; 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Fireside Theater, 1983-1989 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Five Squad Volunteer Ambulance Service, 1976-1986 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Five Quad Ambulance, Undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Flame, The, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Flexible Benefits Program Guidelines, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Flexible Hours (Ad Hoc Committee), 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Flexible Hours Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Food Co-op, 1975-1978 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Food Drive, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Foot Works(Dance Club), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Foreign Student Advisement Center, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Foreign Study And Foreign Students, Committee on, 1963-1966 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Forensics Society, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Fort Orange Village Intergenerational Housing Project, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Forum of Politics, Undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Fossieck Milne Alumni Room, 1995 May 6 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Fossieck Lecture [History Department], Undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Fountain Week, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Fraternity Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Fraternities - Pi Lambda Phi, Undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Frat/Sororities Psi Gamma, 1998 October 11 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Fraternities - Public Service, 1992-1997 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Fraternities/Sororities - SUNYA'S Position, Undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Fraternities - Zeta Beta Tau, Undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Fraternity Zeta Beta Tau, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Frederick Douglas Scholarship - Black Award Form Empire Stare Honor Scholarship, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Freedom Quad, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Free University, Undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - French Club, 1926; 1933 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - French, Department of, Undated (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - French Studies, Dept. Of, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - French Programs, 1965-1968 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Freshman Assembly, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Freshman Camp for Women, 1937; 1957; 1963 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Freshman Orientation Program, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Freshman Seminar Program, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Freshman Studies, School of, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Freshman Week and Weekend, ca. 1954-1963 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Friends of the Farmworkers, 1968-1975 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Friends Organization, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Fulton Hall, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Futterer Lecture, Undated (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Futterer and Paul Pettit, Undated (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Futterer - Gould Fund, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- G, 1888-1998; 7
  - Gallo, Robert Dr., Undated (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Gamma Delta Chi, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Garden Plantings, East and West Courtyard, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Gardens - Uptown Campus Library Garden & Azalea Garden, Undated (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - General College, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - General Education - SUNY, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - General Education, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - General Education Committee, Undated (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - General Education Program, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - General Education Honors Program, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - General Education Honors Program, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - General Education Program, Task Force Review Final Report, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - General Studies Office, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Office of General Studies and Summer Sessions, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Genesis, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Geography Club, 1969; 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Geography, Department of, ca. 1969-1976 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Geography, Department of, 1976 June 8-1985 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Geography, Graduate Study in, ca. 1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - German Club, Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - German Intellectual Émigré Collection [Includes Program "Portraying an Epoch"], 1990 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Germanic & Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1963; 1967-1969 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures, Department of, ca. 1976-1984 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures, Department of, 1984 March - 1991 September (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Gillis, Kendra (student), 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Girls' Athletic Association, Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Glen House, Undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Gov. Thomas E. Dewey Graduate Library for Public Affairs and Policy, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Gould, Samuel B., 1965-1966; 1968 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Gouraige, Ghislain, Undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Office of Graduate Admissions, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Graduate Education and Research, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Graduate School of Public Health Sciences, Undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Graduate Student Association, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Graduate Student Employees Union, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Graduate Student Organization, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Graduates, Their Accomplishments, 1888 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Graduation Committee, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Grant Opportunities for Women and Minorities, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Grant Received by the University at Albany, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Great Decisions Groups, Undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Great Danes, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Great Lakes Research Conference, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Greek - American Society, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Greek & Cyprus Student Association, Undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Greek Student Organizations (social), 1991; 1954 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Green, Jerry E., Undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Greenberg, J. Mayo, Undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Grievance Procedures, Undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Grievance Procedures, 1988 September; 1990 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Grouper Law, Undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Gudykunst, William B., Undated (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Guerrin, Robert E., Undated (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Guidance and Personal, Department of, Undated (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Guinness Day, 1985; 1988 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Guitart, Jorge Miguel, Undated (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Gullotta, Frank Paul, Undated (Box 13, Folder 48)
- H, 1844-2004; 8
  - Haboush, William Joseph, Undated (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Hadassah Vocational Education Bookshelf. Gift of Class 1970 of Milne School in Memory of Ina Abrams (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Haggerty, John Joseph, Undated (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Half - Century Club, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Louise De Angelis Lecture Center, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Hall of History, Undated (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Hamilton, Harris, "Self-Effort", 1892 March (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Hall - Oppenheim, Regina Librarian, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Hall, Ethel (Class fo 1920, Suffragette), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Hamilton, LaVernne, Undated (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Hamilton, Thomas Hale, 1959 October (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Hamilton Hall, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Hanani, Yehuda, Undated (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Handbook For Student Teachers, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Handicapped Students, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Hanks, Jane Richardson, Undated (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Hanson, Patricia A., Undated (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - The Harassing Phone Call, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Harness Racing Club, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Harris, Ann Sutherland, Undated (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Hartigan, John R, 1976-1991 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Hastings Murphy Scholarship, Undated (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Hawley Building Windows, 1985; 2016 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Hawley Building Murals - William B. Ingen, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Hawley Building Morals see: Hawley Library Murals, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Hawley Information, Gideon, 1770 July - May 1874 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Hawley Hall Named for Gideon Hawley, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Hawley Windows, Undated (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Haywood William & Eleanor, Undated (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Healey, James Francis, Undated (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Health& Counseling Services, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Health And Drug Education Council, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Health Plan For Students, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Hebrew Club, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Hebrew Project, Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Hedges, Roman, 1989 January (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Hegde, Krishna G., Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Helios: From Myth to Solar Energy, 1978 March 16-1978 March 18 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Hemenway, Curtis Leland, Undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Henry, Joseph, Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Henry, Joseph Bicentennial Conference, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Henry Joseph Conference, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Henry Bicentennial Conference, 1997 December 2 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Henry Bicentennial Conference, 1997 December 2 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Herkimer Hall, Undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Herman, Robert S., Undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Herriot, Arthur W., Undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Herzel, Roger Williams, Undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Hester, Donald G., Undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hetter, Frank E., Undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Higgins, Bryan Paper by Gwynn Lee Jenkins, "The Power of Words and the Practice of Dialogical Anthropology: Oral Texts about the deaths of Bryan Higgins, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Hilltop House, Undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Hindelang Criminal Justice Research Center, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Hispanic and Italian Studies, Department of, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Hispanic and Italian literature, Department of, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Historic Albany: Its Churches and Synagogues, Undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - History Department, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - History Department - Fossieck Lecture, 1984 April 6 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - History Department Lecture Series, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - History Society, Undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - History of SUNYA, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - History of the University, 1844-1929 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - History of the University, 1934 December; Undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - History of the University, Friends of the Library Sesquicentennial Historical Essay Contest, 1993 November (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - History of the University, Friends of the Library Sesquicentennial Lecture Series, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Hitchcock, Karen R Inaugural Reception and Dinner 7 Nov. 1996 (Invitation + RSVP) (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Hitchcock Inauguration Paperweight, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Hohaus, Reinhard A., 1939 November (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Holiday Sing, Undated (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Holmrich, Dennis, 1972 November 20 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Holocaust Remembrance, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Homecoming Committee Planning Booklet + Photos Gift of James Doellefeld, Asst. V.P. for Campus Life 7/26/93, 1972 October 20-1972 October 22 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Homecoming, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Honors Convocation Committee, 1965; 1966 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Honors Convocation, 1994-1999 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1965 April 25-1989 May 20 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1990 May 19-1993 May 15 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Hostage Crisis, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Hostage Crisis - Aftermath Reproduced from Album(Clipping Files) of Professor Hans A. Pohlsandor 11/30/91, 1994 December 14 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - "How a University Landed $850 - Million and counting", The Chronicle of Higher Education, 2003 February (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Hudson - Mohawk Association of Colleges and Universities, Undated (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Hughes, Langston - Includes books by Hughes + State College News + ASAP articles re Hughes + Hughes visit in 1945, Undated (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Office of Human Resources management, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Office of Human Resources management, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Human Rights Association, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Human Resources Procedures Manual, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Humanistic Studies, Institute of (For programs and announcements of symposiums see Asclepius, Helios, Apollo Agonists), 1977-1983 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Humanities 245, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Humanities Committee, Undated (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Human tech Semester Calendar of Events, 2003 April (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Hurd Reading Room Murals, Undated (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Husted, James W., Undated (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Husted Hall, Undated (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Husted Fellowship, Undated (Box 14, Folder 62)
- I, 1911-2014; 9
  - Ideals of the College, Undated (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Improvement of College Teaching Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Improvement of Undergraduate Teaching, Committee on, Undated (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Inauguration President Robert J. Jones, 2013 September 21 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - India Association, Undated (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Indian Quad, Undated (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Indian Quad, Undated (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Industrial and Technical Education Department, 1911 (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Information Science And Policy, School of, Undated (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Initiates For Women, 1996 March 12 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - Initiates For Women, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - "Initiatives For Women", 1993 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Initiatives for Women Senate Resolution, 1999 October 7 (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
  - Initiatives for Women Assembly Resolution, 1995 April 18; 1995 April 25 (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - Initiatives For Women Annual Summer Celebration, 2014 July 17 (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Innovative and Development, Office of, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Institute for the Advancement of Health Care Management (School of Business), 1993 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Institute An Research on Women, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Institute for Cypriot Studies, Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Institute for Government Executives, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Institute for Mesoamerican Studies, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Institute for Traffic safety management and research, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Highway Safety Forum on the Advertising of Alcoholic Beverages, Proceedings, Albany, N.Y. (Institute for Traffic Safety Management), 1993 February 2 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Institute for Research on Women (IROW), Undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Institutional Funds Report of SUNYA Committee On, Undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Institutional Services Office, Undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Instruction, Task Force on, ca. 1968-1970 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Instructional Computing Information Exchanges (Computing Services), 1989 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Instructional Resources Planning Study, Undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Intensive English Language Program, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Intensive English Language Program, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Interact, Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Interfraternity Council, 1954-1958 April (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Interfraternity Council, 1959 April 15 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Interim Report - Field Expedition #4, 1961 November 8 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Interim Report - Field Expedition #6, 1966 May 1 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Interim Report - Field Expedition #8, 1968 May 1 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Interim Report - Field Expedition #89, 1969 May 1 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - International Conference on Women and Development Focus on Latin America and Africa, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - International Development Program, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - International Film Group, 1961; 1971-1977 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - International House, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - International Programs, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - International Programs, Office of, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - International Socialist Organization, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - International Students, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - International Student Association, 1971; 1975; 1977 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - International Student Office, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - International Student Office, 1970 July 27 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - International Student, Office of, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - International Students, 1995 September (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - International Student Services, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Inter - Sorority Council, 1962-1963; 1979 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Intervarsity Christian Fellowship, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Introduction For Prospective Students, An, Undated (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Inuit Association, The, Undated (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Investigations Involving Human Subjects Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Invest Club, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - IRIS, Undated (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Irish Club, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Islamic Student Assoc., 1976 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Italian - American Student Alliance, 1971-1974; 1989 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Italian Club, Undated (Box 15, Folder 48)
- J, 1932-1995; 10
  - Japan Culture Club, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Jawbone Reading Series, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Jazz Society, Undated (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Jewish Defense League, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Jewish Holidays, Observance of, Undated (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Jewish Presence at the University Exhibit, Undated (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - "Jews of Northeastern New York"Conference, 1993 October 16-1993 October 17 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Jewish Students' Coalition, ca. 1971-1976 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Jewish Students' Coalition, 1977-1993 April (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Johnson Hall, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - D. Bruce Johnson Lecture, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Joint Admissions Dual Degree Program, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Joint Appeal, Undated (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Joint Committee On Procedures, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Journalism Program, 1971-1984 April (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Journalism Program, 1984 April-1985 August (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Judicial Affairs Office, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Office of Judicial Services (Mediation), 1990 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Judicial Workshop Steering Committee, 1970 October-1971 (Box 16, Folder 1)